

Software Developer (PHP)

Date of birth: May 5, 1981

Nationality: Thai

Address: 29/71 Soi Rewadi 35, Tambon Talat Kwan, Amphoe Mueang Nonthaburi, Nonthaburi 11000

Phone: 090-992-9885 Email: natthawat.lek@gmail.com

Summary

MartialStatus: Single



I'm a software developer with more than 8 years experience in front-end development. My strongest skills are in PHP, Drupal, HTML5/CSS3,.Net(C#) and have lengthy experience in Cloud Computing services like Amazon S3 and EC2. My experiences include developing cross-browser and cross-platform compatible solutions and have worked closely with many clients to understand their requirements.

Technical Proficiencies



- PHP, C++, C, Java, HTML5, CSS3, Drupal,.Net(C#)
- JavaScript, Jquery, Json, AJAX
- · Photoshop, Dreamweaver, Eclipce
- Amazon S3, AWS EC2, Google Analytics, Google map API
- SQL, Mysql, Oracle

Work Experience



Berli Jucker Public Co.,Ltd Sep. 2015 - Present

Senior Software Developer (PHP)

Lanna Softworks Co.,Ltd Sep. 2012 – Aug. 2015

Software Developer (PHP)

ICE Solution Co.,Ltd Aug. 2010 – Aug. 2012

Programmer

Toyota Nonthaburi Co.,Ltd Jun. 2007 – Jun. 2010

Programmer Analyst

3BD System Co.,Ltd Feb. 2006 – Oct. 2006

Programmer

Suranaree Software Engineering Co.,Ltd May. 2004 – Jan. 2006

Software Developer

Education



Suranaree University of Technology 2000 - 2003

Bachelor's Degree of Engineering, Computer Engineering

Uttaradit vitaya school 1996 - 2002

High school education

Bandendan school 1989 - 1995

Elementary education

Language skill



English	Poor	Fair	Good	Excellent
Reading				
Writing				
Speaking				

Interests



Reading
Shopping
Movies



Software Developer (PHP)

Professional Experience @ Lanna softworks Co., Ltd

Legalzoom UK – Web application (www.legalzoom.co.uk)

I worked with three developers and two testers for two years on this project. LegalZoom is a popular website that offers legal documents and support online for any type of legal documentation needed in Europe, Britain and United States. I was responsible for developing the front-end and backend for contents updates in the application. The challenging part about the project was learning about Amazon Web Service, S3 and new tools about content management system that help me building web page is faster, it is called Drupal version 7.

r	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
ar rt	- Create front end coding following the mock-up from designer.	PHP, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Json,
d	- Modify and customize modules in CMS (Drupal 7).	Drupal7
S	- Update the content following the files from client.	
(- ie	- Optimize the pages for faster loading time.	
g	- Responsible for implement SEO per requirements.	
ıt		
g		

Legalzoom US – Web application (www.legalzoom.com)

I worked with two developers ,3 testers and one scrum master for one years on this project. LegalZoom is a popular website that offers legal documents and support online for any type of legal documentation needed in Europe, Britain and United States. I was responsible for support for fixing bug and data fix. The challenging part about the project was learning about MS-SQL

ne	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
ct. gal	- Create data fix script usign SQL with MS-SQL.	SQL, MS-SQL, JavaScript
gal	- Update Js script	
ed		
ug		
ct		

Professional Experience @ ICE Solution Co., Ltd

MK System – Web application

I worked with one System Analyst for one year on this project. The project was about made for the company's Key Performance Index (KPI) for the restaurant. I was responsible for business function coding by PHP programming language and building the report with SQL script.

า	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
e	- Custom function to calculate KPI data and store into database.	PHP, Zend Framework, JavaScript,
n	- Create report to show KPI's data.	Jquery, Json, Ajax and MySQL
g	- Test function before pass it to system analyst.	

Paper - Web application

I worked with two System Analysts on this project for 6 months. This project is called the name by Paper, it was a web presentation made specifically for the sales team to present the products with their customers. I was responsible for developing the front end and back end of the application for the product detail.

t	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
J J	- Develop front end to show product detail - Develop back end	PHP, Zend Framework, JavaScript, Jquery, Json, Ajax and MySQL
ō	- Test function and pass it to system analyst if it's work or fix bug if it has the any errors.	



Software Developer (PHP)

Professional Experience @ ICE Solution Co., Ltd

Made to order - Web application

In this project was about the application for clients make a books order. And sales team of DHA Siamwalla, the stationery vendor, will be verify the order and pass it to the factory. I was responsible for back-end and front-end. I worked with two System Analysts on this project for 3 months.

5	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
4	- Develop front end and back end.	PHP, Zend Framework, JavaScript,
r	- Test function and pass it to system analyst if it's work or fix	Jquery, Json, Ajax and MySQL
1	bug if it has the any errors.	

Taher – Web site (http://tsfe.org/taher)

I worked with 3 developers for 1 year on this project. The project was for an organization that focus was on raising money for education. I was responsible for make a web page from the PSD wireframe, the design file had been make from Photoshop and created the back-end system to help user can access to this system for update the contents. What was interesting about the project was the working with the foundation for education.

t. My r	role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
r	eate the web page from the wireframe with HTML/CSS.	PHP, Zend Framework, JavaScript, Jquery, Json, Ajax and MySQL
d - Tes	st function and pass it to system analyst if it's work or fix if it has the any errors.	
s n		

Inden - Web application

I worked with 3 developers and 1 System Analysts for 4 months on this project. This project was for Rajabhat Maha sarakham University to manage the training budget of employees. I was responsible for custom the business logic function to store data with the training course, training cost, training places and how many the employees are in the training course. What was challenging about the project was the new learning with method to generate the PDF files from PHP.

ts	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
or ne or	- Develop function to store training data into database with PHP.	PHP, Zend Framework, JavaScript, Jquery, Json, Ajax and MySQL
h	- Create function to general training form to PDF.	
id e. w	- Test function and pass it to system analyst if it's work or fix bug if it has the any errors.	
m		

Kreeed.com - Web site

I worked with 2 developers for 1 year on this project. The project was about online deal for products and services. I was responsible for back-end to call payment gateway API. What I was challenging about the project was knowledge about the method to communicate with the payment gateway API.

My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
- Develop back end to communicate with payment gateway API.	PHP, Zend Framework, JavaScript,
- Test function and pass it to system analyst if it's work or fix bug if it has the any errors.	Jquery, Json, Ajax and MySQL, Payment Gateway API



Software Developer (PHP)

Professional Experience @ ICE Solution Co., Ltd

lamtrend.com – Web site (www.iamtrend.com)

I worked with 5 developers for 2 years on this project. The project was about social network to help user sharing anything that they would like to share. I was responsible for HTLM/CSS and front-end developed to communicate with Google map API. What I was challenging about the project was learning about the method to communicate with Google map API

_		
5	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
	- Develop front end with Google map API and back end.	PHP, Zend Framework, JavaScript,
k	- Develop web service using SOAP.	Jquery, Json, Ajax, Google map API
5		
1		

Professional Experience @ Toyota Nonthaburi Co., Ltd

Bill Management System – Web application

In this project has a one developer that me. I worked for 4 months on this project. This project was about the system to tracking the mile of the cars in the company. When the employee need to uses the company's car they have to fill up the data into the form and then the official will be record the start of mile and record the end of mile when the car turn back. The next step after the car turn back to the office, the official will be record the data in to this system and run the report at the end of the month to review the oil costs. I was responsible for get and analyze requirement from users and design the wireframe and created the web page from wireframe to the HTML/CSS. The next step, I had custom the function using PHP. What I was challenging about the project was learning with the get requirement steps.

	<u> </u>	
b	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
t	- Get requirement, Analyze requirement and design database.	PHP, JavaScript, Mysql
9	- Modify existing parts of application, testing, debugging.	
е	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement	
f	president data manifectance on energy requirement	
1		
S		
ร า		
b		
9		
j		
t		
t		

ISD Request System - Web application

In this project has a one developer that me. I worked for 6 months on this project. This project was about the car insurance tracking system, this project will be help user to store car insurance data into database and generate the reports for the user. I was responsible for created the reports following the employee requirement using SQL script to query data from tables and present the data that I have query from tables in HTML format. What I was interesting about the project was the knowledge about the insurance process and challenging on the SQL script about how to write the query to run faster and use the less server memories.

d	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
ıt ill	- Get requirement, Analyze requirement and design database.	PHP, JavaScript, Mysql
0	- Modify existing parts of application, testing, debugging.	
I	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement	
е		
y		
e		
ıs		
е		
e		
n		



Software Developer (PHP)

Professional Experience @ Toyota Nonthaburi Co., Ltd

Purchase Order System – Web application

In this project has a one developer that me. I worked for 4 months on this project. This project was about the purchase car parts for the customer, this project will be help the company's customers to access this web page to purchase the car parts what they want. I was responsible for get and analyze requirement from users and design the wireframe and created the web page from wireframe to the HTML/CSS. The next step, I had custom the function using PHP. What I was interesting about the project was the knowledge the business process with the purchase system.

d	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
ıt	- Get requirement, Analyze requirement and design database.	PHP, JavaScript, Mysql
it is	- Modify existing parts of application, testing, debugging.	
t.	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement	
nt	mprement and maintenance on energy equilibrium	
d		
e		
о. е		
e		

Assets System – Web application

In this project has a one developer that me. I worked for 4 months on this project. This project was about the system for tracking the company's asset such as the computers, printers, cars etc. This project will support the employee in general administrator department to know about the location of asset and who was responsible on this assets. I was responsible for get and analyze requirement from users and design the wireframe and created the web page from wireframe to the HTML/CSS. The next step, I had custom the function using PHP. What I was challenging about the project was how to design the friendly UI with the user.

ed	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
ut as	- Get requirement, Analyze requirement and design database.	PHP, JavaScript, Mysql
ill	- Modify existing parts of application, testing, debugging.	
or nd	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement	
le		
nd		
ge		
, 1		
as		
ne		

IP Management System – Web application

In this project has a one developer that me. I work for 3 months on this project. This project was abo the system to help IT supporters to manage the ne IP address for the new user in the company and th will be record the program utilities that they have installed into the computer for the user. It will help fully when the company need to be repair install new operating system, IT supporters v search for the computer data in this system to set the IP address and install the program utilities. I w responsible for get and analyze requirement from users and design the wireframe and created the w page from wireframe to the HTML/CSS. The ne step, I had custom the function using PHP. Wha was interesting about the project was the knowled about the IP generate and IP classes.

ked	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
out	- Get requirement, Analyze requirement and design database.	PHP, JavaScript, Mysql
ney	- Modify existing parts of application, testing, debugging.	
nad be	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement	
by		
will		
tup		
vas		
om		
veb		
ext at I		
dge		
age		



Software Developer (PHP)

Professional Experience @ Toyota Nonthaburi Co., Ltd

Insurance System – Web application

In this project has a one developer that me. I worked for 6 months on this project. This project was about the car insurance tracking system, this project will be help user to store car insurance data into database and generate the reports for the user. I was responsible for created the reports following the employee requirement using SQL script to query data from tables and present the data that I have query from tables in HTML format. What I was interesting about the project was the knowledge about the insurance process and challenging on the SQL script about how to write the query to run faster and use the less server memories.

d	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
ut ill	- Get requirement, Analyze requirement and design database.	PHP, JavaScript, Mysql
0	- Modify existing parts of application, testing, debugging.	
I	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement	
ie		
'n		
e as		
je		
ne		
ın		

Professional Experience @ 3DB System Co., Ltd

Agricultural Futures Trading – Web application

I worked with 1 developer for 6 months on this project. The project was for Agricultural Futures Trading. I was responsible for make a web page from the wireframe. What was challenging about the project was the learning programming language is Delphi.

is	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
es n	- Get requirement, Analyze requirement and design database.	PHP, JavaScript, Mysql, Delphi
е	- Modify existing parts of application, testing, debugging.	
S	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement	

Professional Experience @ Suranaree Software Engineering Co., Ltd

Human Resource Management – Web application

I worked with 6 developers for 3 years on this project. The project was about the human resource management, in this project is contain with pay roll, employee history, training history. I was responsible for coding the business process using java and create the web page using JSP. What was challenging about the project was the learning about pay roll system and learning about Javascript.

S	My role and responsibilities	Technologies Utilized
9	- Develop web application for back office.	JSP, Java, JavaScript, Mysql
,	- Design user interface.	
t	- Modify existing parts of application, including encoding,	
s t	testing and debugging.	
	- Implement and maintenance on client requirement.	
	- Cooperate with other developers and system analyst of team.	